

Ang Yi Xin ul/ux Designer

Analytical designer with 9 years of experience in designing products for public services and games on mobile and web. Seeks to resolve real world challenges through design. Aspires to craft intuitive and simple products that has deep impact in people's lives. Able to hustle, prototype and conduct trials to test product hypothesis. Able to code HTML, CSS and some Javascript.

Contact

4 +65 91731259

angyixin@gmail.com

www.artylope.com

Skills

Competitive Analysis
Heuristic Evaluation
Customer Journey
Personas
Prototyping
User Flows
User Interviews
User Research
User Testing
Visual Design
Wireframes

Tools

Sketch Invision Photoshop Illustrator After Effects Premiere Pro HTML CSS Javascript

Interests

Photography
Drawing
Swimming
Travel
Interior Design
Mindfulness

Work Experience

UX Designer

Nov 2014 - Present

GovTech Singapore (previously IDA Singapore)

Work along side Public Officers, Designers, Software Engineers, Product Managers and Data Scientists to conceptualise, prototype, develop and launch citizen-facing products and tools for public officers.

Parking.sg - Lead Designer. Worked with cross-agencies stakeholders (MND, HDB, URA) to trial, develop and successfully launch Parking.sg mobile app to replace parking coupons. By June 2018, Parking.sg is the top government app with 700k iOS and Android App downloads and 8 million parking sessions and has an average ratings of 4.1 stars on Apple App Store and Google Play Store.

Beeline.sg - Lead Designer. Beeline started as an experiment to demonstrate data-driven bus planning. Within 3 years, it expanded into a suite of tools for transport companies to improve commuter experience. Major innovation includes public route suggestions and clustering capability, ticket booking, bus tracking and monitoring, and a crowdstarting mechanism to activate new bus routes. Currently, Beeline runs 200 express bus routes monthly and is adopted by major companies (e.g. Grab, SMRT, Comfort Delgro, JTC).

Digital Content Strategist/Game Artist

Oct 2012 - Sep 2014

Singapore University of Technology and Design (SUTD)

UI/UX Design, Game Art, Web Design for One Upon Light Game on Sony Playstation. Set up and facilitated an annual internship programme on game development - "Game Innovation Programe". Designed online and offline touch points of the candidates evaluation process.

Game Artist May 2009 - Sep 2012

Singapore-MIT GAMBIT Game Lab

UI/UX Design, Game Art, Web Design for Social Game on various Facebook and iPhone/iPad Games. Launched Game titles includes Nightmare Duel, Snap Escape, and Snap Escape: The Epic Swing. Experience in Scrum and agile development practice.

Courses

Certificate in User Experience Nielsen Norman Group	2017
User Experience Design General Assembly Singapore	2015
User Experience and Creative Data Lab Hyper Island	2014
Specialist Certificate in Visual Communication I Nanyang Academy of Fine Arts	2012

Education

Bachelor of Fine Arts (Digital Animation), 1st Class Honours

2005 - 2009